Amanda Seal's first mistake was going to
do this interview with Shannon sharp for
somebody who supposedly understands
journalism this platform should have
been your last resort or it should not
have been even on your radar Amanda
Seal's second mistake was thinking that
Shannon sharp had any knowledge or any
awareness to be able to understand her
when she's talking about her experiences
with racism I have so many question
questions and I'm not sure we're going
to get a lot of answers but let's talk
about it know what
[Music]
got so what's going on you all we got to
talk about Amanda Seal's recent
interview with Shannon sharp on Club sh
Shay a 3our interview um and apparently
some things were left out but 3 hours
and a couple of minutes is a lot and I
had to sit through all of that
because truly I want to understand what
is going on with Amanda seals like I
find her fascinating as a person who has
you know talked about her experiences
and how people do not like her and how
she is outspoken and that may be the
reason and I think the to be honest I
think the reason why is because
sometimes I feel like I am that person
like what is the reason why some folks
do not like me and whatever da d d da
and I wanted to
understand her like I wanted to live
through her and see what is going on and
I to be honest took a lot from this and
I think I see what is truly going on so
less than 20 minutes in this interview
we are already hearing Amanda Seal's
name that she has been diagnosed with
autism now later to come to find out she
was not clinically diagnosed she was
self-diagnosed and Amanda seals being a
person of her caliber and her word play
She's a comedic she's a actress like she
has all of these things even Shannon
sharp took almost a minute and some
change reading through all of her
accolades this person who she throughout
the interview she talked about how
special and how intelligent she was did
not understand how saying that I have
been diagnosed with autism will come off
to a group of people when people hear
someone say hey I've been diagnosed with
said thing people expect you to go to a
doctor or a professional and they
diagnose you with that I have been
diagnosed with ADHD I was diagnosed as a
child with ADHD or hyper something or
whatever my kindergarten teacher had a
conversation with my parents and talked
about that I do not pay attention in
class and I be drifting off and I'd be
looking outside and I just do not be as
connected and my parents took me to a
doctor and you know he diagnosed me my
parents never did allow me to get on
medication they just didn't believe in
it at the time and I understood the
reason for because you know they didn't
trust doctors pushing medications
especially on black kids even when I
talked about my experiences of ADHD I
never did say I was diagnosed because I
haven't gotten an official diagnosis I
understand and see the symptoms and I
may fit these but I need to seek a
professional and that's what I did and a
professional diagnosed me so if I was to
ever talk about it I will say before I
got diagnosed that I looked at these
symptoms and I fit a lot of these things
but I don't know I might be I might not
be but I need to talk to a professional
Amanda seals being a word Smith should
have been able to word that better and I
think that's very telling of her
character because there are a couple of
things throughout Amanda Seal's
interview and also throughout her career
that there is a lack of
accountability that is happening
repeatedly you're not going to be
friends with everybody just because you
were friends with someone 20 years ago
does not mean you going to be friends
with them 10 years from now things
happen but we have to take into
consideration some of the things that we
may have done to put ourselves in this
situation how old were you when you got
diagnosed and did you always feel that
you was different and you felt something
was was wrong what was today today is
Thursday the 18th so
42 and however many days until I I was
just recently diagnosed okay we get a
response from Amanda seals online and
saying that she was self diagnosed and
that she did not want to spend
$10,000 getting diagnosed or what have
you or whatever Amanda seals is a
actress she has accomplished all of
these things I don't think that $110,000
is keeping her from getting diagnosed I
don't think if Amanda seals is truly
seeking for understanding of why people
don't like her because the autism was
brought up in the very beginning and the
autism sets the stage for Amanda Seal's
experience with all of these things that
has caused her grief or whatever people
not liking her and caused her some type
of you know made her feel some type of
way it has set up the stage that Amanda
seals may have experienced these things
because she does have autism and she's
not aware of what is going on she talked
about that and later come to find out
that she said she was diagnosed but it
was a self diagnosis and it's just not
working and now she's going at it with
Shannon sharp now I'm not a fan of
Shannon sharp and there is several
critiques for Shannon sharp in this
interview that jump out automatically to
me but now she's into it with Shannon
sharp Amanda SE reached out to Shannon
sharp to be on this platform again
Amanda seals is intelligent as she is I
don't understand why she thought that
this was the place to have a
conversation like this something is as
delicate as what she has
experienced she is sitting next to
Shannon sharp who is not a journalist
she went on this platform like she s
after him to be on this platform now
Amanda seals dealt with a lot of
backlash recently and some bullying to
me from several blackowned black
Publications wrote about her and talked
about why people don't like her I'm not
the biggest fan of Amanda seals but
Amanda seals has not done any harm she
has not done any harm she's not the
quote unquote female Diddy she's not
directly harmed anybody from our
knowledge we've not seen any
conversations of that it's just like
runin people not agreeing da d d da
and that is not harm and I just don't
think that a public call out is
necessary but understanding how
Hollywood works and you know how things
move it was an abuse of power and it was
just unnecessary there have been several
other um specifically black men who have
done some very harmful stuff to black
women and these Publications have not
been quick to write articles or pieces
about that so I'm not understanding
what's going on um and Amanda Seal's
talked about she had every right to talk
about her experience dealing with that
and she was owning the moment like
people were supportive and people were
like yes like even folks who were not
fans people who had critiques for her
was like this is not right this is not
cool this is not d d Amanda seals then
starts to do what she does and she
became self-absorbed to the point that
now she's doing this podcast with a
person who is not journalist somebody
who's not necessarily going to question
and push back as hard on her because
they are not aware of the things that
have happened Shannon sharp is not aware
of some of the things that Amanda seals
has been called out about particularly
the conversation about her response to
Samir rice Tamir Rice's mother and how
she responded to Samir rice and Def
of Sean King who has been called out for
fraudulent Behavior so this happened
some years ago let me read the the the
message because it was originally on
Instagram where she commented so Samir
rice Tamir Rice's mother posted this on
Instagram and she basically called out
Sean King why do you think it's
important to tell folks we had a
conversation well we talked and
everything was said was very toxic and
uncomfortable for me to hear that you
raised additional money and then said
you did not want to bother me personally
I don't understand how you sleep at
night I never gave you permission to
raise nothing along the United States
you robbed me for the D of my son you
gave me a cop and donut conversation all
lies Sean please stop thinking we on the
same page as a white man acting black
you are an impostor that cannot be
trusted my son 12 years old and doj
needs to reopen his case period to me
Human Rights was violated why would you
soever make it about you you are self
self-centered person and God will deal
with you white man and this was posted
on you know Instagram and Amanda seals
you know posted this on the blog um who
reposted it and she said this it's no
secret that I have s i SK meaning Sean
King however bigger picture nobody finds
it someone odd that she just out the
blue going out of her way and being
given every platform with no receipt
shown to call out one by one black
activist SL organizers that have been
the visible faces of the movement just
food for thought Amanda seals being a
word Smith understanding language all of
the things this is her response to a
mother who lost her
child this is her response there's no
Grace there's no care there's no
anything Amanda seals is basically doing
everything to everybody else that she's
claiming folks are doing to her there
was no Grace this is someone who has
lost it who has lost her child a lot of
people cannot relate to that especially
this situation this is a tragic
event and I'm using my words carefully
because again this is
YouTube Amanda Seal's response was
tacky and people responded to it and
they called her out they called her out
and folks since then have not mess with
her they said they will never forgive
her for that and even people tweeted and
said I don't want to watch this three
hour interview until she talks about
what she did to Samir
rice and we saw her response to the
conversation she was um attacking
Samaria rice what I asked valid question
that ended up being proven by the way I
as a valid question don't we think that
there's something worth questioning and
why this this woman whose son was 100%
unjustly K the police don't we think
that there's something to be said for
like why are all these media Outlets
like giving her a platform to accuse all
of these people that are the leaders of
movements for
fraud not really saying much she
basically is doubling down on what she
said and said that you know it was
justified Amanda seals is talking about
celebrity activist grifters that's who
she's talking about and the folks who
really do the work responded and ate her
up about it instead of taking this time
on this show because Shannon Shar does
not know what's going on to address it
she basically said I was justified it's
about her it's about her being right and
I've said this a couple of times um and
I want to say it again sometimes for us
content creators sometimes for us with
platforms and stuff who speak on things
whatever you want to call it sometimes
it's best for us to just shut up
sometimes sometimes it's best for us to
just shut up again Community the same
way if I have a thought about something
I'm calling my friend aan if I'm having
a thought about something I'm calling my
friend Harold if I have a thought about
something I'm calling my friend C if I
have a thought about something I'm
calling my friend who I can have these
conversations with and we go back and
forth and if I'm wrong they're going to
tell me I'm wrong if they agree they
push back I am not running to have the
conversation on social media because I
understand I have an audience I have a
platform and I do not want it to be
received that I am being any other the
things that people might take it out of
context now some folks still do but I am
aware of how these things work and I
have true Community to have these
conversations Amanda seals seems to not
have that because I don't want a got you
moment in the response to a mother who
has lost their child to something as
violent as that Amanda
seals said that she did not understand
colorism she thought that it worked in
Reverse I want to know how recent this
is because there are a couple of people
who I follow in respect who talk about
colorism and antiblackness that she has
had blocked in response to them
critiquing her about her conversations
around colorism Amanda seals is a
lightskinned woman with straight
curly
hair and that
matters that
matters and I think that Amanda seals is
still thinking that reverse colorism
exists even a little bit I know folks
who will say well I I actually dated
somebody who said that there's no such
thing as reverse colorism but then went
on to describe reverse colorism Amanda
seals is not going to do that but the
way she is speaking about her
experiences and even when we're talking
about the treatment from Issa
Reay it doesn't sit right for me again I
don't know Amanda seals I don't know
Issa Ray I can't say that Easter Ray did
not do these things or wasn't you know
mean or whatever I don't know when I see
Easter Ray on Instagram social media
whatever she is laughing one thing ister
R going to do is laugh she going to
smile she going to show them beautiful
teeth period And I was listening to
Amanda Seal's talk about her experience
with Issa Ray she talked about Issa Ray
having uh this website where she had a
show on and that she had the show on Isa
Ray's website and when people talked
about it they said it was Issa Ray Show
and Amanda steel said she reached out to
ISA Ray and said Issa can you say that
this is not your show can you let them
know and she said Issa told her
no I you know it may have happened
period there's other things that Amanda
seals is talking about with her
treatment on insecure she's talked about
nobody on the show really liking her she
talked about one of the people on the
show had a um a child with somebody on
the show and that people were talking
behind this person's back and you know
she had to put them to the side and said
hey you need to take care of this
because folks are talking behind your
back and you know they're saying some
stuff and she said you know the guy told
her like I appreciate you for keeping it
real and she said that this person end
up siding with the folks who did not
like her and critique on her and all of
the things then she goes on she talks
about the famous incident everybody's
been talking about then she goes on to
tell us a story that she said a couple
of times about her not getting into this
emy's party this black emy's party um
and the party is being thrown by Isa R's
um publicist Vanessa and she said that
you know Vanessa told her that she
wasn't on list like she's not going to
come in d d and Issa you know told
Amanda like girl I'm not don't bring me
in it like Amanda asked her what's going
on uh like you need to have a
conversation with us because your girl
do not like me and Isa said that ain't
got nothing to do with me I can honestly
I can see somebody saying that like girl
you know I ain't getting in there which
tells me that it might be some other
stuff that's going on that something
that like hey you know I think this not
going either way both y'all just don't
like each other I'm not going to be
exhausting myself doing that work like
girl y'all do that Amanda also shares a
story of her you know being assaulted by
the bouncer who is kicking her out and
she wants to know why she was you know
you know kicked out and that bouncer
should never put his hands on her Point
Blank period Point Blank period I think
my thing is I'm not going into a place
that someone is telling me I'm not
invited I I'm not even if a friend say
hey girl come on to the
party I am listening to Amanda SE tell
the story and she says she's walking off
she's leaving and that the person is you
know checking in and d and comes back
and get her I want to know if I'm not
going I'm like girl they ain't let me in
I'm leaving I'm not forcing my way into
a place where a person has told me I'm
not like I'm just and this is not like a
diner that is refusing black folks this
is not a like it's not one of those like
I this is not a heel for me to well they
don't like me I just okay I don't want
to be in this place I don't but Amanda
seal should have never experienced it
with their bouncer or whatever she said
she had a conversation with Isa race
publicist Vanessa and Vanessa called her
uh and she tried to tell Amanda like
girl the reason why I a you know let you
in cuz I don't like you Amanda says she
hungs up the phone and you know home
girl calls back Vanessa calls back and
says girl you don't want to know like
what's going on and Amanda says she
don't like you need to talk to your
therapist
and for me and I understand like she
experienced this stuff with the bouncing
and all the other stuff like being
assaulted whatever the story that she
has shared about that
I when somebody says like they don't
like me or something like that I may no
like there are some folks who don't like
me there are some folks who do not like
me um and I have an idea why they don't
and I would say okay it must be this or
but I will still be curious of what was
it because people will say that they
don't and then when they have to name
necessarily what it is they can't really
name something that was harmful they
can't like I don't like it such and such
a like and I always come back to that's
okay I'm not for everybody like I'm just
not and that's okay it's not enough of
these folks who do not like me to keep
me from doing what I'm doing obviously
there are a lot of people who do enjoy
me I have a nice decent size following
on every platform even Tik Tok and I
don't even really use it like that so
I'm not going to be worried about the
small percentage of folks who do not
like me I'm not going to be hyperfocused
on these people Amanda seal seems to do
that she seems to do that a lot and
Amanda seals is very accomplished she's
right now on a tour Comedy Tour she has
bookings all the way until the middle of
August she has had a special on HBO she
has had what a book she's probably
working on another book she has had
plenty of things it doesn't look like
that she's going without food shelter
she's able to purchase her mother her
house she's taking care of her her
mother I'm just not understanding what
is going on and why we so hyperfocused
on these people who don't Amanda seals
every 6 months or every year is on a
podcast talking about her experiences of
people not liking her and I need for her
to let it go and I get that massage
award exists I get it how Shannon sharp
engaged with her and dismissed her
conversations about her experience with
race dealing with kids Shannon sharp was
getting frustrated because he is a
person that is not here for the
conversations about race like people I'm
starting to like call it what it is like
people who like oh here y'all go again
they already tired of it because for
somebody like me even if it's something
that might jump out the window I'm like
H I'm like let me let me hear you out
let me hear what you're saying I'm not
dismissing I'm like hm let me hear these
folks don't want to because it's already
too much like y'all bring it up the race
card they do that the conversation that
I had about like um Beyonce and sacred
and stuff that showed us everything how
people feel about texturism futurism all
the things I did a whole video about
that shout out to y'all for watching it
and comenting people were already
annoyed they did not but when I read the
tweets and stuff that were called out I
was like home girl might have a point I
thought originally receiving everybody's
comment on it I thought that it was out
the way but I said let me see for myself
let me really cuz I want to understand
even if somebody is jumping out the
window how often do we see someone say
something and then 20 30 years later
it's like oh wow folks have been writing
and talking about this this
anti-intellectual stuff that is going on
is starting to jump out like it jumps
out so much so when Amanda seals is
dealing with someone who is about to
tell her this is the reason I just don't
see why she didn't want to listen to it
I just I don't understand it I feel like
there is more missing from the
conversation um and I don't think we
will ever get that other piece because
these folks are not going to like come
out and say anything like these folks
are doing good like the folks that
Amanda SE are calling out you know they
they don't have to be held accountable
to talk about this um they don't they're
not going to come and do no podcast
they're not going to ruin their image
and their brand talking about this and
it seems as though Amanda seals is in
the right because she's the only one
talking I'll give you an example of
another light-skinned person who's doing
all the talking and people think that
he's winning a rap beef right now Amanda
seals is doing all the talking and she's
still not really getting it like she's
still not getting it again the
conversation about her dealing with the
racist
kids like Shannon sharp didn't
understand what key is a key is like
again Shannon sharp is that person who
is
not he's not interested in com like he's
tired even when Shannon shark pushes
back and says that oh all the folks
online like that that's all people
online doing in response to Tamir Rice's
mother Samir
rice she should have shut that down she
should have shut that down like hey
that's not what it is and she did a
little bit but Shannon shark doesn't
again have the capacity to talk about
these
things does not he was not even aware of
it he is responding to a woman who has
lost her child and he automatically oh
them they just a post on the internet
cuz everybody hating on each other it's
like no everybody's not hating on each
other like we want to make these social
media platform like Twitter and stuff
like folks commenting and giving
opinions like oh everybody's mad and
stuff on
Twitter everybody is not mad everybody
is talking and we are consuming Millions
not even Millions honestly put some way
sh form hundreds of thousands of folks
talking at any given
moment opinions Twitter was created for
that for us to have opinions for us to
talk I don't understand how folks are
upset at folks having opinions you all
are creating content podcast for us to
listen to but you do not want us to be
critical of it or whatever it happens I
have had my videos critiqued or whatever
it is what it is part of the
conversation you either take it or you
leave it that's why when I put out my
content it's finalized I am making sure
before I get in from this camera that I
know what I'm talking about and if I did
misspeak or say something that didn't
make sense I don't mind being you know
pulled back in um and you know she is
sitting next to somebody who doesn't
understand these things I want to go
back to the EA Ray conversation because
she made a comment about protecting Issa
she's not protecting Issa anymore so
I've never talked about this
publicly because it has always been
incredibly important to me to protect
Issa because I know that Issa is doing
something within this business that so
few people get to do and it's not
something I desire to do like I'm I'm
not interested in getting a $100 million
do production deal like that's not a
life that I want for myself but I know
that her role is very important and so
I've always protected Issa um however
there's just been enough instances at
this point where I should have been
protected by Issa and I wasn't I'm
really confused at Amanda Seal saying
that she's protecting Issa and she's
been talking about this for how long and
the way she's centering herself in this
conversation of protecting
Issa is telling us like what is the
purpose like it's still on her like I am
the one doing this D it's always about
her I'm protecting Issa and no way did
did we find out or learn
anything that really could have been
quote unquote damaging to Issa so what
is she protecting her from and are you
protecting her in this very moment
you're not you're even talking about the
need to protect her so it is quite
literally the opposite and the way a
Mana seals use protecting Issa you would
think that Issa has done something very
harmful to the point that oh my gosh
like if this information comes out it
can be devastating how often have we
heard people women being in situations
or whatever and say that they were
protecting their image of their husbands
or whatever how often have we seen that
like I'm protect like it came off like
she was saying she's protecting her from
some tea coming out all the stuff that
Amanda seals is naming isn't no harmful
stuff has Amanda seals been black ball a
conversation I don't feel like she's
been black danda has had a lot of
success she's been dealing with you know
a lot of things she's had plenty of
things go on she's on tour she's doing
this and that I don't think she's been
black balled I don't think she's been
black balled I think that Amanda seals
feels as though she's supposed to be
bigger than what she is and she's
supposed to have even more opportunities
and I will say this and Amanda S I say
this in a very respectful way I do think
that you have some talent I think that
you definitely are funny I definitely
think that you have the Charisma but
there are a lot of other folks who are
excelling you in that department um I
think you're good and I think
unfortunately that you looking the way
you do look makes you feel as though you
are deserving of these
things uh more than other folks and I
think that is in it self a conversation
about how colorism shows up and how
certain folks believe certain things
because of they've been told Amanda
seals was on my brother and me one of my
favorite shows growing up when I was a
child I watched it and Amanda seals
being on there playing the character of
like I think she was the sister if I'm
not
mistaken and the two boys I watched that
show and as a child I thought to myself
that these kids don't look like me but
this is like I'm glad that they're black
like I knew that texturism was a thing
at a very early age being raised by a
dark skinned mother who has experienced
colorism in her you know life period I
understood things like I understood like
wow like and I also had a brother who
had the same texture of hair as the
folks on the show and Amanda SE talks
about she did really good for the part
she you know she did she Excell like
she's excelling and I never hear Amanda
seals necessarily and I wish she talked
about it more that sometimes you do get
picked because of colorism sometimes you
get seen because of colorism because of
that like yes you are talented but
you're being seen because of your color
your skin we cannot remove that you can
be talented there are other folks who
are talented too but they're not seen
because of how colorism Des desire and
antiblackness shows up you have
benefited from colorism all of your life
you were a child actress from the
beginning all these things I feel like
that your experiences with all these
things is the reason why you're having
some of these issues
because you have benefited from colorism
for so long that I feel like that you're
not used to being told necessarily no I
don't think and I and I've had
conversations about this in the past I
want you to all to think about how many
times we've seen folks get online and
they talk about them being single and
how long they have been single and the
reasons that they say they should not be
single is because they are attractive
and d d think about Miss Netta think
about how people have responded to miss
Netta and Charles been in relationship
and saying that if Miss Netta can find
love I know I can what what am I doing
wrong and it's often time people who are
desirable like having that conversation
because their belief is that being
desirable is enough to be in a
relationship like that is all that
matters like I am being chosen like why
am I not being chose and this is why we
have conversations about desirability
because it it shows up outside of the
bedroom and it shows up in real life and
I feel like that it shows up in Amanda
seals and her experiences I think again
Amanda seals does not take into account
of what she has done sometimes and I
think that's telling on her everything
can't be everybody I've not heard Amanda
seals talk about what she may have done
wrong to put herself in a situation or
how she made somebody feel who doesn't
mess with her she's not talking about
that you've been having experiences like
this since you were young people not
like the teacher not like you I get it I
had some like some teachers who did mess
with me dealt with a racist teacher
dealt with a homophobic I've dealt with
I get it but there are some teachers who
loved me and who
and there was some things that I was
doing that that's why they don't mess
with me like I did this and that and
they just ain't really feeling it and
they can not choose to mess with me like
that's just is what it is but Amanda
seals doesn't understand that and I
think she does not understand that
because she has not been told no that
many times I like how often do we think
about when folks who work harder like I
think automatically about my one of my
favorite anime is Naruto Naruto grew up
like you know mes messed up like he
didn't have family he didn't have he was
just a throwaway and he wasn't very
talented this is an anime character he
wasn't very talented he had to keep
working and keep pushing himself he
didn't get it right the first time and I
think about folks who are always told
yes who are always seen and they're so
used to that that when somebody else is
excelling they don't understand why like
they can't get it I think about folks
who excelled in high school who went to
college and could not do it like could
not do it because they were really push
they really struggled because they were
used to being the top of the class they
were used to being the one that knows
everything and they are not they can't
deal with the fact that they don't and
Amanda seals no shade comes off like
Hermione Granger from Harry Potter no
shade like she comes off like hermion
and she talked about being Miss no all
and all the other stuff and I I think
that it's not necessarily Amanda seals
dealing with being misn all and all the
other stuff I think it is you know
colorism I think that how folks receive
her and been around her um and she has
this complex about herself we all feel
like we are you know all of us should
feel like we are good D all the other
stuff like period but I think that you
know it's different for people like
Amanda seals who are always used to
being the chosen person the desired
person in the room who has benefited
from colorism and I don't think that
Amanda seals has taken that into account
I don't think she's taking how she moves
yes people do not like loud black women
they don't they really don't like loud
dark skinned black women they literally
do not like loud fat dark skinned women
unless they're making jokes about
themselves so I do think that of course
massage Noir plays into how folks
critique and how they resp on to Amanda
seals and I also think that Amanda and I
know that Amanda seals benefits from
colorism so her
experiences although she is experiencing
anti-blackness and misogyny she still
benefits from being light-skinned and I
don't think that in some of these
situations she's being truly honest
about some things that she may have done
again I don't agree with folks writing
articles and and pieces and stuff about
her but I think for some people the
response to the Samir rice situation
made people be over her I think things
like the Samir rice
situation is one of the reasons why
folks you know are just not messing with
you sister I think that that is telling
of your character and people don't have
to mess with you after that they just do
not people do not had to come back and
support you after you've done something
like that and you could have took this
time on this show to you know have a
conversation about it and apologize
truly apologize in aone for it and you
did not do that and I think you did not
do that because of your inflated ego
that's all I got I am done talking about
this tell me what y'all think about the
conversation did y'all watch the
interview let me know in the comments
and I'll talk to you later bye
[Music]
n